两位 我需要你们听我说
Girls, I need your attention.
你大多情况下还需要儿童餐椅
You also need a booster seat for most places.
不 我出来是要告诉你们重大消息
No, I came out to tell you some big news.
你今天穿着这件毛衣来上班
You also came out when you wore that sweater
已经算出柜了
to work today.
约翰·梅尔接受Details采访时就穿的这件毛衣
John Mayer wore this sweater in Details.
今晚 我们要尝试家庭式服务
Tonight, we are trying family-style service.
我以为家庭式服务是我被逼给叔叔
I thought family-style service was what I had to do
干的那种活儿
with my uncle.
我的家庭式更偏向于"百乐餐"...
Well, my family-style is more "potluck"...
享乐为主 吃饭为辅
heavy on the pot, not so heavy on the luck.
一家人干嘛要来这儿?
Why would a family come here?
要是我在这儿看到孩子 我就报警了
If I see a child in here, I'm calling the police.
就像关爱锁在高温车里的狗狗一样
It's like seeing a dog locked in a hot car.
鸡块 家庭式的
Chicken cacciatore, family-style.
肝和洋葱 家庭式的
Liver and onions, family-style.
意大利面和肉丸 我家式的
Spaghetti and meatballs, my family-style,
也就是肉丸有点小
which means the balls are kinda small,
但面条特别长
but the noodles are extra long.
你们拿大碗盛出食物
You bring out the food in large bowls
然后顾客们自己动手
and the customers serve themselves,
就跟我雇了你们俩 顾客也要自己动手一样
as they've been doing since I hired you two.
好主意 Han
Good idea, Han.
餐厅的食物确实得放在一个桶里...
The diner food does belong in a big bowl...
厕所马桶
the toilet bowl.
真不知道你叔叔看上你什么了
I don't know what your uncle saw in you.
破产姐妹花 第四季第22集 季终集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: SW沫   校对: 女王影
翻译: 波特妹子  CD猪  TG薇  SP飘  K9奥
Max 我刚在手机上
Max, I just found something
看到非常烦人的东西
very upsetting on my phone.
又一张免费的U2专辑?
Another free U2 album?
更糟糕
Worse.
而且比收到朋友的电子邀请看即兴演出还惨
And worse than an e-vite to a friend's improv show.
是一封糕潮店总经理的邮件
It's an e-mail from the managing director
说他看过我们的销售业绩
of all The High restaurants saying he's seen our sales
并对我的表现非常失望
and is disappointed with my performance.
删掉...
Duh-lete...
就像我删掉
like I do with all
跟我睡过的家伙们发的
the "disappointed in your performance" texts
"对你的表现失望"的短信一样
I get from guys after sex.
抱歉 哥们! 我的咪咪太重
Sorry, gents! My boobs make a promise
后背承受不来
my bad back can't deliver.
那些低销售额不是我们的错
Those bad sales numbers are not our fault.
我们的店可是开在机场啊
Our unit's out at the airport.
这不是我的责任
Well, I'm not taking ownership of this
因为我的宝贝不在机场
because my unit is not at the airport.
而是放在我的床头柜里
It's in my bed table drawer.
我是经理 都怨我
I'm the manager. It's on me.
就跟这污渍一样 就是洗不掉
As is this tartar stain. It just refuses to come out.
让人还以为它父母是基督徒(不敢出柜)
You'd think it's parents were Baptist.
那么 经理 我明天得早点下班
Well, Manager, I need to get out of there
做Sophie的结婚蛋糕
early tomorrow to do Sophie's wedding cake,
还因为你当老板超烦人的
and also because you're annoying as a boss.
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
一步 两步 三步 四步 是我 是我 还是我...
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me...
我喜欢做新娘 你都不用假装
I love being a bride. You don't even have to pretend
对别人感兴趣了
it's about anyone else.
跟我有钱那会儿一样
Kinda like me, when I was rich.
你现在也没好到哪去
Pretty much every single day still.
一个好消息 一个坏消息 好消息是
Good news, bad news. The good news is
皮疹没有传染到下肢
the rash is not spreading past my nuts.
这竟然是好消息
And that's the good news.
坏消息... 我们预定仪式用的
Bad news... the wedding donkey we booked
婚驴死了
for the church service died.
我来问个显而易见的问题
I'll ask the obvious question.
驴死跟皮疹有关吗?
Did it have anything to do with the rash?
我们该怎么办?
I mean, what are we gonna do?
没有畜生走过礼堂的婚礼
It's not a traditional Polish wedding
就不是传统的波兰婚礼
without an ass walking down the aisle.
我觉得Oleg可以扮演畜生的角色
I think Oleg's got that covered.
妹子 我们需要畜生 而你有匹马...
Girls, we need an ass, you have a horse...
同样的家庭 但不是血亲
same family, but not related,
就像朱莉-皮特家的孩子似的
like the Jolie-Pitt kids.
不行 小栗子是我的孩子
No way. Chestnut is my baby.
我们本来要付那驴一千大洋
Well, the donkey was getting a thousand bucks.
亲孩子也得干活
Baby's gotta work.
天 卖蛋糕的速度比第三季
Wow, business is slower than the third season
纸牌屋的节奏还慢
of House of Cards.
你知道什么受人欢迎吗?
You know what's doing great business?
就是我的新基达档案
It's my new Grindr profile.
我把网名改成"舔鸡高手"了
Changed my screen name to "Suction Junction".
隔壁该死的肉桂蛋糕把我们的生意都抢走了
That damn Cinnabon next door is taking all our business.
什么样的屌丝会喜欢那个
What kind of low lives would prefer those
而不选我们精致的糕点呢?
to these fine desserts?
我找到去肉桂蛋糕厨房的密道了!
I found a secret pathway to the Cinnabon kitchen!
闪开 贱人!
Move, bitch!
不是吧? 连你也这样? 我不明白
Really? You too? I just don't get it.
这是嗜好 跟吸毒一样
It's an acquired taste, like crystal meth.
真是
Ugh.
这下好了 服务生又迟到了
Great. My waiter's gonna be late again.
"我被堵在安检队伍里了"
"Held up at the TSA line."
这就是我雇一个叫Mohammed Machdinajihad
That's what I get for hiring an airport waiter
机场侍应生的下场
named Mohammed Machdinajihad.
哦 快看 Ronnie 新店哎
Oh, look, Ronnie, a new place.
我看到了 Bonnie 我就在你旁边你呢
I see it, Bonnie, I'm right next to you.
这过去不是我们起飞前
Didn't this used to be the bar we got wasted in
买醉的酒吧吗?
before our flights?
我记不得了 因为我喝醉了
I can't remember. I was wasted.
欢迎来到糕潮...
Welcome to The High...
高质量精致糕点
the finest in high quality desserts.
我们还有酸奶 卡布奇诺 拿铁 咖啡
We also have yogurts, cappuccinos, lattes, coffee,
草药茶 或者醒脑水
herb teas, or smart waters.
我有没有提到我们还有无线网热点?
And did I mention we're a Boingo Hotspot?
别这么激动
Take it down a notch.
你比在今夜秀上的安妮·海瑟薇
You're selling it harder than Anne Hathaway
还要卖力
on The Tonight Show.
哦 你好 我只是来看看 不买东西
Oh, hi, I'm not here to buy, just to look.
我在节食... 从九八年就开始了
On a diet... since 1998.
老天啊 那些看起来好棒
Oh dear lord, those look amazing.
- 我能闻下吗?  - Bonnie 别
- Can I just smell a piece?  - Bonnie, don't.
你停不下来的 等巴黎航班飞到半程
It'll get you going, and then halfway to Paris,
我就会看到你在客舱里大口吃着薯片
I'll find you in coach binging on a bag of Sun Chips.
我最喜欢我工作的这点了
That's my favorite thing about the job.
说起巴黎
Oh, Paris reminds me.
我买过两张去巴黎的头等舱票...
I bought two first class tickets to Paris...
用三张六年内利息增长百分之二十的
on three credit cards that will escalate 20%
信用卡买的... 总之...
over six years... anyway...
我必须退掉它们
I really need to return them.
你们航空公司的退票期限是多久?
What's the window on that with your airline?
一个月... 跟我能长久保持
A month... about the same amount of time I have
这种假笑的时间是一样的
until this fake smile finally falls off my face.
女士 我们可是空姐
Lady, we're flight attendants.
如果你不能保持假笑的话
If that smile falls off your face,
你就只能去西南航空找工作了
you're gonna have to get a job at Southwest.
你为什么要退掉? 你不喜欢巴黎?
Why are you returning them? You don't like Paris?
我爱死巴黎了 但长话短说...
J'adore Paris, but long story short...
我来说吧 因为她讲不清楚
Uh, I'll make it short because she's incapable
而且还会说更多糟糕的法语
and will throw in lots more of that fake French.
当时买票是因为我要去登机口见一个
Bought the tickets so that I could get to the gate
和我上床的男人
to see a guy I was banging.
我懂你
I hear ya.
我有次在行李车上藏了十二个小时
I once hid in the luggage cart for 12 hours
就为了跟一个在这里海关工作的
to do it with this cute guy
帅小伙上床
who works at Customs here.
对 Rick 他现在在干什么?
Oh, right. Rick. What's he doing now?
干我啊 隔周周四
Me, every third Tuesday.
别让我等着 女士们
Ahh, don't leave me hanging, ladies.
如果我们不是刚在酒友俱乐部...
Ah. If we hadn't just read Lean In
我是说读书俱乐部... 读了"向前一步"
in our wine club... I mean book club...
我们会很嫉妒你们呢
we'd be real jealous of you gals.
我们一直梦想着在机场开一个小店
We always had a dream to open a shop at the airport.
不管开什么店 都不要开在肉桂蛋糕店旁边
Well, whatever it is, just don't open
因为失败闻起来
near a Cinnabon because failure smells
跟肉桂一样难闻
a hell of a lot like cinnamon.
这是前往巴黎的
Final boarding call
第24次航班的最后登机通知
for flight 24 to Paris. Final boarding call.
最后登机通知? 我们得快点了
Final boarding call? We better hurry.
哇 这里的所有东西
Wow, everything looks so much smaller in here
比我记忆中的还要小
than I remembered it.
就像回高中母校的时候...
Like returning to your old high school...
或者是高中前男友的屌一样
or your old high school boyfriend's penis.
我的可不是 我去的是普通高中
Not mine. I went to an urban high school.
这是什么怪味道?
What's that weird smell?
可能是牛奶吧 放在这里太久了
Probably that milk. It's been in here so long,
它自己的照片都印在盒子上了
its own photo was on the carton.
不 在这里 真的很刺鼻
No, it's over here. Really pungent.
太棒了!
Yes!
额... 我可能欠你俩点租金
Mm... I might owe you two some rent.
除非你们想引进大麻
Unless you wanna settle in weed.
我一直想引进大麻
I always wanna settle in weed.
实际上 我计划着退休后搬进大麻呢
In fact, I plan to retire there.
橱柜里有大麻?
Marijuana's in the closet?
这比Meredith Baxter-Birney出柜还令人震惊
This is more shocking than Meredith Baxter-Birney.
我当时想 反正你俩放弃了纸杯蛋糕的生意
Look, I figured since you two abandoned the cupcake shop,
这地方又空着
this space was available.
而且 自从我到了七十岁
Also, I stopped asking permission for stuff
我再也不征求别人同意了
when I turned 70.
我们没有放弃
We did not abandon it.
我们只是三个月没有留意它了
We just haven't paid attention to it in 3 months,
就像我不留意大腿中部以上的任何毛发一样
like me with any hair above my mid-thigh.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
你穿着那条裙子弯腰的时候
When you bend over in that skirt,
看起来像是阿特·加芬克尔正在从你两腿中间钻出来
it looks like you're giving birth to Art Garfunkel.
一 二 三 四 是我 是我 还是我!
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me!
太好了 Earl 你在这儿
Oh, good. Earl, you're here.
是的 我在这里 不要告诉我的前妻们哦
Yes, I am. Don't tell any of my ex-wives.
Earl 你肯赏光
Earl, would you do me the honor
明晚挽着我走过红毯吗?
and walk me down the aisle tomorrow night?
Sophie 真抱歉
Sophie, sorry.
我不知道你爸爸去世了
I didn't know your father was dead.
他是在和Oleg见面的时候去世的吗?
Did he die upon meeting Oleg?
不 他还活着
Oh, he's not dead,
但是我不想被一个铁肺呼吸器抢了风头
but I'm not getting upstaged by an iron lung.
Earl 你怎么能拒绝
Well, Earl, how could you say no
这么一个真诚的邀约呢?
to such a heartfelt request?
我很荣幸 Sophie
I'd be honored, Sophie.
就像婚礼谚语所说的
Like the wedding saying goes,
一些旧的 一些新的
Something old, something new,
一些借来的
something borrowed,
和一个黑人
and someone black.
Caroline 瞧
Oh, Caroline, look.
这是给小栗子的粉丝带
Here are the pink ribbons for Chestnut.
小栗子得裹上这些娘气的丝带?
Chestnut has to be covered in girly ribbons?
不能这么对我的小男子汉
I can't do that to my boy.
我加价50
I'll throw in another 50.
我想"马"和"妓女"听起来
I guess there's a reason "horse" sounds
这么相像是有原因的
so much like "whore."
嗯 我们都得六点出发去教堂
Now, we're all gonna leave for the church at 6:00,
但是我跟Earl说的是4点钟
but I told Earl 4:00,
因为 嗯... 你们懂的
'cause, well... You know.
- # 嗯哼哼哼 #  - 这是怎么回事?
- # Mm-hm hm hmm #  - What's happening over there?
Max 你在哼歌!
Max, you're humming!
什么?
What?
拜托...
Please...
我不是那种会哼歌的人
I am not a hummer.
我是说我可以开一辆悍马
I mean, I'll drive in them,
可以送一辆 但是我自己不会哼歌
I'll give them, but I am not one.
天啊 我在哼歌! 我哪儿出了毛病?
Oh, my God, I am humming! What's wrong with me?
下一步我该做什么 微笑?
What am I gonna do next, smile?
就是这样! 今日特别优惠
That's right! Today's special promotion,
进出只需五分钟 超时五折
in and out in five minutes or your dessert is half off.
瞧着吧 肉桂蛋糕店
Eat it, Cinnabon.
梨挞和咖啡 快来 这边记着时呢
Pear tart and a coffee. Come on, I'm on a clock here.
谁点了该死的梨挞和咖啡?
Who had the damn pear tart and a coffee?
Max 赶紧的! 五分钟 进出!
Max, hurry! Five minutes, in and out!
嗯 你唯一不需要向我解释的事情
Yeah, the one thing you don't have to explain
就是"进出"
to me is "in and out."
我需要帮助! 我没说自己动作很快的
I need help! I never said I was fast.
我所有的高中辅导员倒是卸货很快
All my high school guidance counselors did,
但我不是啊
but I did not.
我去把正在休息的John叫来
I'll go get John off break
因为我的服务生还没来
because my waiter still isn't here.
这整个的中东麻烦
This whole Middle East situation
简直对我太不方便了
is just so inconvenient for me.
好吧 我们现在真的出了点状况
Okay, now we have a real situation.
你打人了 该死 Max
You hit someone. Damn it, Max.
不是我 是Sophie
It's not about me. It's Sophie.
她的礼服从波兰运过来了
Her gown arrived from Poland
但是卡在这边的海关了
and it's stuck in customs out here.
我的礼服!
My gown!
我美丽的礼服!
My beautiful gown!
天啊! 我的礼服!
Oh, my God! My gown!
好吧 她真的很生气
Wow. She is really upset.
是超级生气
Really upset,
因为我都没开扬声器
'cause this isn't even on speaker.
是啊 很糟糕 但乐观点
Yes, it's awful, but look on the bright side.
我们那些绝对十分丑陋的伴娘礼服
Our certain-to-be-hideous bridesmaids dresses
也一起卡在了海关
are stuck in customs too.
不 那些已经到了
No, those arrived.
该死! 先是中东麻烦
Damn it! First, it's the Middle East,
现在是那些礼服
now those dresses.
我都没法休息了
I cannot catch a break.
哇 这地方人满为患啊
Wow, this place is packed.
还记得我们吗? Bonnie和Ronnie?
Remember us? Bonnie and Ronnie?
我们见过的
We knew you when.
嘿 等等 呃 Ronnie
Hey, wait, uh, Ronnie,
你是不是说过你上过一个海关小哥?
didn't you say that you boned a guy in customs?
那是Bonnie 我是有原则的...
That was Bonnie. I have standards...
而且他也不喜欢我
and he didn't like me.
明白点说 我确实和海关小哥做过
To be clear, I did have sex with the customs guy,
但不是在海关
but not in customs.
是在一间母婴厕所里
It was in one of those family bathrooms.
听着 你们可不可能帮我们
Look, is there any way you could help us
从海关那边弄出一个包裹呢?
get a package out of customs?
等等... 我今天穿了什么内衣?
Wait... What bra am I wearing?
手到擒来!
Oh, done!
John 我们要走了 你来负责
John, we're leaving. You're in charge.
Max! 我们现在可不能走
Max! We can't leave right now.
婚礼今晚才举行 我们现在还在
The wedding's not till tonight and we're in the middle
店铺促销中 而且我们要输了
of a store promotion and we're losing.
你知道我会杀了你的吧?
You know I'm gonna kill you, right?
只不过要想想怎么下手
I just have to figure out how.
让头号对手把你的项链
Top contender is hooking your necklace
拴在前门 再把你推上去
on the front gate and pushing up.
我们尽量待晚点
We'll stay as late as possible.
只要抄起装Sophie婚纱的盒子 然后跳上地铁就行了
Just pick up Sophie's dress box and hop on the subway.
小菜一碟
Easy peasy.
关门请当心
Watch the closing doors, please.
呃... 哦...
Ugh... oho...
为什么就是不能来个一碟小菜?
Why is nothing easy peasy?
关门请当心
Watch the closing doors, please.
我可当心呢!
I am watching the doors!
怎么会不当心 它们快把我的盒子吃了
It's hard not to. They're about to eat my box.
对 真好笑 先生
Yeah, real funny, sir.
有个女孩说"吃了我的盒子" 成熟点吧
A girl said, "Eat my box." Grow up.
天! 一件婚纱怎么会大到这样?
Jeez! How could a dress be this big?
这还只是头纱
This is just the veil.
我得从包里掏点东西
I have to get something out of my bag.
你先自己撑会
Hold this by yourself for a second.
找不到了 这个 帮我拿着这个
I can't find it. Here, take this.
这又是什么?
What is this?
一百刀的零钱
A hundred dollars in change.
婚礼上用的 波兰传统是
We need it for the wedding. It's a Polish custom
要把零钱撒到新娘身上
to throw change at the bride.
撒零钱? 带牲畜?
Loose change? Live animals?
究竟是结婚还是斗鸡啊?
Is this a wedding or a cock fight?
Max 好重啊!
Max, this is heavy!
你到底要在包里掏什么呀?
What do you have to get out of your bag?
- 很重要的东西  - 什么呀?
- Something important.  - What is it?
我吃剩的肉桂蛋糕
The rest of my Cinnabon.
Max 那可是我们的对头!
Max, that's our competition!
我们就是输在这垃圾上
The reason for our failure is that piece of crap.
我是说...
I mean, I ca...
我的神呀 好吃到飞起!
Oh, my God, this is delicious!
不! Max 他拿了我们的钱包
No! Max, he's got the money bag.
不... 不! 不许捡!
No... No! No, no, no!
这是我们波兰新娘的钱!
That is our Polish bride money!
都退开!
Back off!
今天谁都不许跟我搞事儿
This is not the day to the screw with me.
我已经跌到事业谷底
I'm at the business bottom
而且2011年来我就没啥可失去了
and I've had nothing to lose since 2011.
皇后广场到了
Queen's Plaza.
好呀 屋漏偏逢连夜雨
Yup. That's what would happen next.
她们在后台磨蹭什么?
What's the hold up back there?
大家在赌我会不会卷了婚礼礼金
People are placing bets that I'm halfway to Reno
再带个妓女去里诺
with a hooker and the wedding cash.
里诺: 美国内华达州的赌城
放轻松 从地铁上下来
Relax. After that subway,
Max和Caroline要点时间梳妆打扮
Max and Caroline needed some time to freshen up.
她们来的时候 臭的就像那块
They came smelling like that diner cheese
我跟你说还能凑合用的奶酪
I tell you all is still good.
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
我们简直是Sophie第二! 我松了一口大气啊
We look just like Sophie! I am so relieved.
还以为我会穿得太隆重 结果只是胸不够重
I thought I'd be way overdressed but I'm just under-boobed.
没错 我们太赶时间了
Yeah, we were in a hurry
要不然我肯定会"借她一码"
or I would have loaned her a cup of mine.
不错啊
All right.
Oleg 别这么看我们
Oleg, stop looking at us like that.
有啥关系 我要跟你结婚的
It's okay. I'm marrying you.
你们几个看起来就像四大高人
You guys look like the Four Tops.
Four Tops: 美国1953-1997年间的一个摇滚乐队
好吧 只有两个高人和一个垫底的
Well, two tops and a bottom.
Sophie不想让你见到她 Oleg
Oleg, Sophie doesn't want you to see her.
骑上小栗子走婚毯吧
Jump on Chestnut and start down the aisle.
小栗子 我对不住你 宝贝
And Chestnut, I'm sorry, baby.
我知道你从来不想驮人
I know you never wanted to do drag.
Han 你得拿着这个
And, Han, you're supposed to take this
以防马在路上屎兴大发
in case something happens in the aisle.
伴郎变铲屎郎啦
This just went from best man to worst job.
# 嘿! #
# Hey! #
嗨
Hi.
觉得怎么样 女孩们?
What do you think, girls?
我看起来像纯洁吗?
Do I look like a virgin?
我听见号声了 该我上场! 上啊 女孩们 上!
I heard the tubas. That's my cue! Go, girls. Go!
天啊!
Oh, God!
她的礼服差点害死我们
Her dress almost killed us
现在真害死Earl了
and now it killed Earl.
太感谢了
Thanks.
还以为我死定了呢
I thought I was a goner.
该说誓词了
Time for the vows.
呈上皇冠!
Bring the crowns!
戴冠之人
And crowned is married...
喜结连理
with honor.
哦...
Ohhh...
将皇冠举于新人头顶
Raise the crowns to their heads.
开始吧 没有梯子的话
Better go. This is as good as
这已经是最好的办法了
it's gonna get without a ladder.
我 Sophie Kachinsky...
I, Sophie Kachinsky...
愿意嫁Oleg Golishevsky为妻
take you, Oleg Golishevsky
相亲相爱
to love and to cherish,
相伴相随
to have and to hold,
誓言忠于彼此
never to leave your side
至死也不分离
'til death comes to take me.
我 Oleg Golishevsky
I, Oleg Golishevsky,
愿意娶Sophie Kachinsky为妻
take you, Sophie Kachinsky,
相亲相爱
to love and to cherish,
相伴相随
to have and to hold,
誓言忠于彼此
never to leave your side
至死也不分离
'til death comes to take me.
我宣布你们正式结为夫妻!
I pronounce you husband and wife!
Max 该丢硬币了
Max, now you throw the coins.
说来话长
Long story.
哇 小妞 手脚挺利索的嘛
Wow, girl, your fingers work fast.
肯定是多年
Must be from years
开裤裆拉链练就的手活...
of opening those 501 button-fly jeans...
我的 还有别人的
Mine and others'.
Max 我等够了 我现在就要
Max, I'm done waiting. I need that piece
那片蛋糕
of cake right now.
刚刚在空中真是惊险
We just had a close call in the air.
惊险到我们险些把手指
So close, we gave the finger to the pilot
献给隔壁飞机的驾驶员了
in the plane next to us.
我们差点坠机了 而且我可不想
We almost crashed, and I didn't wanna
在飞机坠落时喊
go down screaming,
"我真该开家日间托儿所!"
"I should have opened a daycare center!"
我坠机一般会喊"你没给咱买晚饭!"
I usually go down screaming, "You didn't buy me dinner!"
Bonnie 我们承认吧
Bonnie, let's admit it.
我们永远不会为梦想放手一搏的
We're never gonna go for our dream,
就像我们一直没去洗肠一样
just like we never went to get those colonics.
如果我们真有做生意的心
If we really wanted our own business,
早就开店了 就像Max和Caroline这样
we would have done it already, like Max and Caroline did.
你说得对 我们开了
You're right, we did.
John 给这两位女士
John, cut these two the biggest piece
切两块这里最大的椰果坚果果仁蛋糕
of coconut macadamia nut cake we have.
天呐 我刚刚好像"高潮"了
Oh my god. I think I just climaxed.
那就提好裤腰带
Well, then pull your panties on
像你过去那样溜之大吉
and slink the hell out like you usually do.
Caroline 我要找你说句话
Caroline, I need to talk to you.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
工作! 我累死了
Working! I'm very sick.
外面的Bonnie和Ronnie提醒了我一件事
Bonnie and Ronnie out there just reminded me of something.
除了我的两位姨度假喝醉那事
I mean, besides two aunts drunk on vacation.
我们有自己的小生意 "糕潮"不是我们的失败
We have our own business. The High isn't our failure.
我们已经有过咱们自己的失败了
We already have our very own failure
就叫"Max自制纸杯蛋糕"店
called Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
而且我们若留下来
And if we stay here, we're building
就是为别人做嫁衣
someone else's dream, not ours.
还有就是 我们要是留了
Also, if we stay,
你的屁股就有房子这么大了
your ass will be the size of a house.
还有 你最近一次在这感到开心是什么时候?
I mean, when was the last time you felt happy here?
就在30秒前 你说这地方
Like 30 seconds ago when you said this place
不是我们的失败所在的时候 我还记得
wasn't our failure and I remembered I was holding
我另一只手还拿着块蛋糕呢
another one of these in my other hand.
咱们离开这机场吧
Let's get out of this airport.
咱们再也不用看尼古拉斯·斯帕克斯写的纯爱小说了
We never have to see another Nicholas Sparks novel again.
首先 咱们得花掉
First, we have to get rid
那两张去巴黎的机票
of those two plane tickets to Paris.
真的吗?
Do we?
我想说 万一失败了
I mean, if we're gonna fail
咱们在巴黎待上一周后还可以继续做吧?
we can still do that after a week in Paris, right?
对哒
Right.
我好激动呃! 人家还没坐过头等舱呢
I'm so stoked! I've never been in first class.
只不过 Max 这是二等舱
Except, Max, this is coach.
我退了一张票 换了另一张票
I got a refund on one ticket and traded in the other
然后买了两张二等舱的票 还付了廉价酒店的房钱
to buy two coach tickets and to pay for a cheap hotel.
我好激动呃 人家从没坐过二等舱呢
I'm so stoked. I've never been in coach.
这样一来
And also so
咱们就有多余的钱花了
we have money to spend.
咱们到了巴黎后 每周只花12刀应该过得去
We should be able to do Paris for a week on $12.
那是当然啦
Of course, we can.
头等舱和二等舱之间有啥区别来着?
What's the difference between coach and first, anyway?
附送香槟
The champagne.
我们稍后为您送上优质饼干(疯子)
We'll be back with the good crackers,
我说的不是我们俩
and I don't mean us.
好啦 合伙人 在这一年里
Well, partner, after all we've been
经历了这么多风雨 不管接下来如何
through this year, whatever comes next,
我感觉自己都做好准备了
I kinda feel ready for it.
机务人员 准备起飞
Flight crew, prepare for take-off.
嘿 你在哼歌
Hey, now you're humming.
有吗?
I am?
嘿 我可以拿这个换啤酒不?
Hey, can I trade this in for a beer?